{"items": [{"question": "showing little emotion", "answer": "phlegmatic", "options": ["phlegmatic", "leonine", "feline", "canine"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "resembling a lion", "answer": "leonine", "options": ["leonine", "feline", "porcine", "canine"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "resembling a dog, loyality", "answer": "canine", "options": ["canine", "feline", "porcine", "vulpine"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "resembling a cat", "answer": "feline", "options": ["porcine", "vulpine", "ursine", "feline"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "resembling a swine", "answer": "porcine", "options": ["ursine", "lupine", "porcine", "vulpine"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "resembling a fox", "answer": "vulpine", "options": ["ursine", "lupine", "vulpine", "piscine"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "resembling a bear", "answer": "ursine", "options": ["pork", "lupine", "ursine", "piscine"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "resembling a wolf", "answer": "lupine", "options": ["lupine", "telephone", "piscine", "pork"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "resembling a fish", "answer": "piscine", "options": ["phonograph", "piscine", "pork", "telephone"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "meat from a pig", "answer": "pork", "options": ["pork", "saxophone", "phonograph", "telephone"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "transmitting speech at a distance", "answer": "telephone", "options": ["saxophone", "telephone", "phonograph", "xylophone"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "any sound reproducing machine using records in the form of cylinders or discs", "answer": "phonograph", "options": ["phonograph", "phonetics", "xylophone", "saxophone"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "a single-reed woodwind with a conical bore", "answer": "saxophone", "options": ["phonics", "xylophone", "saxophone", "phonetics"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "a musical intrument consisting of a graduated series of wooden bars, usually sounded by striking with small wooden hammers", "answer": "xylophone", "options": ["phonics", "xylophone", "carnivorous", "phonetics"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "the study of speech sounds and their pronunciation", "answer": "phonetics", "options": ["carnivorous", "phonetics", "herbivorous", "phonics"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "Teaching reading by training beginners to associate letters with their sound values", "answer": "phonics", "options": ["omnivorous", "carnivorous", "phonics", "herbivorous"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "Feeding only on flesh", "answer": "carnivorous", "options": ["carnivorous", "potential", "herbivorous", "omnivorous"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "Feeding only on plants", "answer": "herbivorous", "options": ["potential", "herbivorous", "potentate", "omnivorous"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "Feeding on both plants and animals", "answer": "omnivorous", "options": ["omnipotent", "omnivorous", "potentate", "potential"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "Expected to become", "answer": "potential", "options": ["potentate", "omniscient", "omnipotent", "potential"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "A ruler who is free by law", "answer": "potentate", "options": ["omnipresent", "omnipotent", "omniscient", "potentate"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "Having unlimited power", "answer": "omnipotent", "options": ["omnipotent", "omnipresent", "omniscient", "fatigue"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "having complete knowledge", "answer": "omniscient", "options": ["flesh", "omnipresent", "fatigue", "omniscient"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "Being present everywhere at once", "answer": "omnipresent", "options": ["omnipresent", "carnal", "flesh", "fatigue"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "Temporary loss of strength and energy", "answer": "fatigue", "options": ["carnage", "carnal", "fatigue", "flesh"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "The soft substance of the body consisting of muscle and fat", "answer": "flesh", "options": ["carnal", "carnage", "carnival", "flesh"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "Relating to the body or flesh", "answer": "carnal", "options": ["carnival", "incarnation", "carnage", "carnal"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "The savage and mass murder", "answer": "carnage", "options": ["carnival", "carnage", "reincarnation", "incarnation"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "A festival marked by merrymaking and processions", "answer": "carnival", "options": ["carnival", "incarnation", "reincarnation", "phlegmatic"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "A man who stands for some abstract idea", "answer": "incarnation", "options": ["leonine", "reincarnation", "incarnation", "phlegmatic"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "Rebirth", "answer": "reincarnation", "options": ["leonine", "reincarnation", "canine", "phlegmatic"], "answer_index": 2}], "title": "Word power Made Easy - Session 41.txt", "total": 31}